Fred Ho Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Additions
  - Recognition & Recommendations, 1988-2002
  - Interviews of Ho, 1994-2002
  - Short Statements, 1993-1998
  - Poetry, 1984-1991
  - Calvin Massey Research, Articles, Tribute, 1984-1990
  - Bill Cole Research & Article, 2000-2002
  - Drafts, 1972-2001; (3 folders)
  - Published Articles, 1982-2002
  - Residency Schedules, 2001-2002
  - Publicity Materials, 1999-2002; (3 folders)
  - Press Clippings on Ho, 1990-2002
  - Sheroes Calendar Research, 1986-2002
  - Communist Party Draft w/ Ho's comments, 2001
  - Article Clippings, undated
  - E-mail News Articles, 2000-2002; (2 folders)
  - Fliers, 1999-2002 (Box 20)
  - Pamphlets, 1999-2002; (2 folders)
  - Magazines, 1999-2002
  - Rescue the Word, Chapbook by Marylin Buck, 2001
  - Monsoon, Journal of Asian American Art & Writing, 2002
  - Back to the Blanket, Cherokee/Native American Journal, 2001-2002
  - Civitella Ranieri, 2001
  - Phonics text?, undated
  - Class papers on crime among girls, undated
  - Tierra y Libertad: Land and Liberty, bilingual play, undated
  - Newspapers, undated; (3 folders)
- Additions—Special Format
  - Cassettes
    - WKCR Interview w/ Fred Ho re: Monkey, 10/96
    - Bill Cole Interview, 2/22/02
  - CDs
    - Radical Radio w/ Fred Ho, 3/30/01; (2 discs)
    - Hardknock Radio presents Mumia Abu-Jamal, 2001
    - Gravity and Chaos, Interview w/ Fred Ho, 2/02
    - Avir (Mitra), 2001
    - Song, Newton & Bynum, Trio Ex Nihilo, 2000
    - Isangmahal arts kollective: omo alagba & all one tribe, 2000
    - Isangmahal arts kollective: muling pagkabuhay ng kaluluwa, 1998
  - VHS
    - Welcome to DV Republic, MNN show, Interview w/ Fred Ho, 1/14/03
    - Television Spot of Fred Ho—Tempe, 9/28/01
    - Passage of Oracles: danscape by Peggy Myo-Young Choy, 2/17/01
    - Battle for the Shaolin Temple, Seattle Internat. Children's Festival, undated
    - Warrior Sisters ASU, Maliha Shah closer version, undated
    - Warrior Sisters Kitchen, 2000
    - Once Upon a Time... Bronx TV, 2/13/97
    - Once Upon a Time... John Harms Center for the Arts, 6/20/99; (3 copies)
    - Once Upon a Time... Guggenheim, Works & Process, 12/13/99
    - Once Upon a Time... Guggenheim, Children Audience, 12/13/99
    - Once Upon a Time... Guggenheim, Dub Dec E, 9/29/00
    - Once Upon a Time... Seattle Children's Festival (close ups), 5/01
    - Once Upon a Time... Seattle Children's Festival (second camera), 5/01
    - Once Upon a Time... Blackman Hall, Boston, 8/18/01